<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
 <rss version="0.91">

 <channel>
 <title>Yellow Indie</title>
 <link>http://yellowindie.com</link>
 <description>Yellow Indie, crafted by Shivek Khurana {}</description>
 <language>en-us</language>
 
 <item>
 <title>twitter redesign</title>
 <link>http://test-yellow.zymichost.com/standalone/twitter_redesign</link>
 <description>
<img src="../../graphics/posts/twitter_redesign.png" alt="New Twitter homepage"/>
Its always good to start up with an image :P</p>
<p>So as expected, the new twitter home page is here, and along has come a Tsunami of thoughts in my curious brain. Why the fuck did they use the marquee tag ?</p>
<p>Its a small lot, so I'm classifying all I need to say under <strong>&#8220; Yack ! &#8221;</strong> and <strong>&#8220; not so yack ! &#8221;</strong></p>
<p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Yacks of new design</strong><ol><li>
All I found was just one, the marquee tag sucks. Earlier all trending topics were browsable at once, but now we need to wait and look at the horrible text. Ridiculous.
-3 for this.</li>
<li><del>That's it</del>
</li></ol></li>
<li><br/></li>
<li><strong>The not so Yacks !</strong><ol>
<li>The color combinations is pretty safe and usual. +0 as nothing new.</li>
<li>The search box is powered with a really cool hover effect, something I've never seen before so +2 for that</li>
<li>Top tweets as Live on <a href="http://www.gowalla.com" title="Gowalla" target="_blank">http://www.gowalla.com</a> nothing new, yet looks good. Another +1 for it.</li>
<li>Look who is here looks nice as well. Good for attracting new users. And the get started now button is OK. Good enough to get another <del>+1</del> +2 rather.</li>
</ol></li>
<li>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
Remove the marquee, you rock. Keep it the way it is &#8220; Boooo! &#8221;
</li>
</ul>
</p>
 </description>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>CM`Screwed me</title>
 <link>http://test-yellow.zymichost.com/standalone/cmscrew</link>
 <description>
I forgot to mention that I hate .php. Don't know why. Its like my soul speaking to me that “ php monster will tear your brain tonight ”. But still as said in my previous article, I gave php powered CMS-es a decent try. My options were very limited as php was all I could opt for (my free host doesn't allow python)
The outcome was similar to a vague expectation. I SCREWED IT. I just gave it up, something I usually don't do. What I did was enough to pump up my curious brain to think what happened. The main reason I found was bad poor .php background. I'm not capable of coding even a single line of php. I gained very valuable experience in these those 49 hours over 2 days. Enough for me righting a review. But I'm not writing one now. Maybe after the doomsday.
If you too are a newbie, but know a bit of php, I recommend textpattern, else Joomla is your engine.
 </description>
 </item>
 <item>
 <title>CMS search</title>
 <link>http://test-yellow.zymichost.com/standalone/cms_search/</link>
 <description>
“ Drupal is the most efficient CMS ever ”, “ Joomla is most powerful ”, “ There's nothing like Wordpress ”. Frankly speaking, all such reviews make me shout, “ WTF ”.
I'm 15, (a great excuse), and I had just heard of a thing called CMS, but never knew what it was, or what its use was. All I knew was html and CSS. Thanks to Sir Tim for my first encounter with CMS. I just got to know that CMS-es are used to manage you site and call in better functionality. I have never used a CMS before, I don't know what it looks like, all I know is that I'm eager to learn something new.
Can't say write anything regarding limitations and barriers put up by my free zymic hosting account. Will update soon.
 </description>
 </item>
 </channel>
 </rss>
